Oh
Was it as good for you as it was for me
Actually Niles I was faking it
Oh
Hi sweetie see some of the kids are going to the Hamptons for the weekend. Oh great. Will there be boys there?
Maybe a few
Parents who cares they'll just get in the way anyway
Go have a blast. We don't have enough to tell your father
Really? Oh sure and when I'm fired and you're in the convent. We'll write each other letters and laugh about this
But Maxwell how can you say no to working with Philippe he's an avant-garde
Genius guilty is charged and I've put a new twist on the tragedy
We follow Romeo and Juliet to heaven and have a happy ending
You're really writing one of the greatest love stories of all time. We're adding a few scenes, but we're taking out others
Which ones the ones that don't work?
Well, I'm sorry fully but we British have a thing about mutilating Shakespeare the Queen comes and hits you with her purse
But I bet you have a big name to star
I'm looking for an unknown a fresh face with a unique voice
I found my Juliet
She was working in a bridal shop and flashing Queen's till her boyfriend kicked her out in one of those crushing scenes
What was she to do? Where was she to go? She was out on her fanny
So over the bridge and flashing to the Sheffield's door. She was there to sell makeup at the father's home. She had style
She had she was there. That's how she became the nanny
She was there that's how she became
Can you imagine anything more ridiculous than me doing Shakespeare? Oh, yes people paying to see it
I'll have you know that in high school. I played the Reverend Mother in the sounds of music
I put a low scoop neck into my nuns have it and those hills were alive
We did the sound of music I played the Baroness
It was an all-boys school, thank God I didn't play the guitar I would have been Maria
Who would do our laundry clean our room we don't know standing foot. Well the same person that always does miles
Besides if I do it. It would only be for a couple of weeks
Actually, I could rehearse while the kids are at school. I think not why thank you not I could use a life outside of this house
Me too, which is why you should let me go to the Hamptons nice try forget it
But miss fine taking care of the children is a full-time job. Oh, and I suppose it was my idea to have three
What you do in your spare time is entirely your own affair
I'm simply trying to protect you from having an embarrassing theatrical experience. You know what that's like. Don't we sir?
You know if some people aren't a little more supportive I might omit them from my Oscar speech
Tony miss fine did win a Tony not an Oscar actually for an off-broadway performance miss fine would win the OB. She's not going to win anything
Well, thank you for that vote of confidence. That's it. I'm playing Juliet and nothing is going to stop me
And I'm going to the hampton down Margaret, okay
Okay, Niles will you play Romeo isn't he too old
Well, actually Juliet supposed to be my age so it's not like France
Perfect for the role
Iwarn you my acting prowess may blow you off the stage. They're still talking about my baroness. I
Can't stop thinking about it, and I didn't even see it
And I spent my summers in Stratford upon Avon. I spent my summers selling a fun. Oh
She does teach the torches to burn bright it seems she hangs upon the cheek of night
I don't I come in here somewhere
Beauty too rich for use for a ride back off Baroness
And by the way, you're supposed to dust the scenery not chew it
Okay, they show me how it's done. Mistress fine. Well, I will if you'll just shut it up it
All for a Falconers voice to lure this tassel Gentile back again
It's gentle not Gentile
How should I know did I look down as tights I
Still can't understand why Philippe would hire miss fine to play Juliet, please only an idiot would hire her to do anything
In the theater
Oh
Mr. Sheffield if you got a minute I could use your help. That's the understatement of the century
Meanwhile if we put an apple in his mouth, we can have a luau
Let me see oh
I just love this play
More torches here are Sarah by my fey it waxes late
That's exactly what I'm talking about with Alice Faye and why she wax under in a party
Oh
Good luck. Sorry. Hey Romeo. It's your Juliet four three two. What took you so long?
All right. So now we're star-crossed lovers. Let's get some physical realism into this
Put you on your balcony
All right now Juliet is dreaming of her Romeo and she says I
I mean
Oh speak again bright angel Oh
Romeo Romeo
Yes. No, maybe we could have a little more lilting just a bit more melodic. Oh sure sure sure
Oh, Romeo
Yeah, just a little too melodic I think let me show you okay
Oh
Romeo Romeo
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name Wow you British guys really know how to play women
We we did this play in college, oh you must have been the perfect Romeo no, I was friar Lawrence actually
That's the problem going to school with Jeremy Irons
Romeo that's my name and
Take all of me
I
Take thee at thy word. Call me but love and I'll be new baptized
You know, if I were directing this I'd go in a whole different direction
I
Parting is such sweet sorrow
Sleep dwell in nine eyes
Peace in thy breast. Oh would I was sleep and peace so sweet to rest
Because this lovey-dovey stuff has just been done to death
You know
I
Spitter
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it now
Of course I'm gonna need a lot of coaching
I
Am Dracul I'm going to suck out all your blood and bury you alive. You don't scare me
All right fine. I'm the CC monster and I'm gonna marry dad and send you away to boarding school
Be quiet
I
Geez dad, you don't scream about it. Look I already sent you to bed five times. What are you doing still up?
Well, maybe that has something to do with a pound of chocolate. I told you not to eat
You know, I think it was a gallon of cola. You told me not to drink
What's your excuse? Well, he took me
Obviously you got out
Just give me one good reason why I can't go to the Hamptons
I won't let you
Margaret you're much too young to go away for the weekend by the time Juliet was my age
She'd already gotten married had sex and died
Well now you see what happens when you don't listen to your father
Niles I'm thinking of changing the children's bedtime. Oh to when sir right after school. I
Can't believe miss fine isn't back yet. I can't believe what's happened to my roast
It's starting to bear a strange resemblance to Hume Cronin. I mean how much rehearsal can one person need?
Right but still
Hi guys for so them I poked dinner is coming right up. Oh
Niles I already ate you couldn't have called
Ruined anyway
Oh, yes, he moody well you are rather late. What are you two on the same cycle?
What's the problem? Oh you couldn't handle the kids don't make me laugh
What do you think the minute you leave the entire house falls apart?
Now don't go in there why not when you the back stairs they're closer nothing. Yes, they are. Oh, so I measured
Oh
This place looks worse when my mother ransacked my bedroom looking for my diary
Well, I was looking for my glasses what you have a reading emergency
So what were you doing all evening? I was at rehearsal. Oh, I called for us was over a date
Well, we went out after ah, who's we?
You know Romeo Mercutio tibbled the gang. Oh
Sorry it was an accident
So was that
Boy, you leave the house for a couple hours. You come back and it's a pigsty
Yeah, well, maybe if you've been here your children wouldn't have been running a muck. Oh
So when they're sweet adorable angels, they're your children and when they're a mock they're mine. You are the nanny
You want me to be now I'm getting one of my headaches
You know what I think you are jealous because Philippe discovered something that was right under your nose and what would that be exactly?
my star quality
That's all I like discovering the atomic bomb sounds good in theory, but millions will suffer
I
Don't bother I'm sleeping on the couch
If we're splitting up I get Niles you couldn't afford him
It's always the butler who suffers
I
I'm working pretend. I'm not here. That's how I get through the day. Oh
Hello Niles
Would you mind telling mr. Sheffield that I'm going to rehearsal
Unless of course he'd like me to sit by his feet and peel him a grape
Well, that's my job, but you can waive the fan
You can tell the nanny that I wouldn't dream of standing in the way of her aspirations no matter how ludicrous they might be
Tell mr. Sheffield that I am a grown woman and can find fulfillment
Any way I choose and that he is a duty hit
To synopsize sir, you are a duty head
So that's the one you choose to repeat
Translators prerogative. I don't think I've ever met a more infuriating irritating woman
Think hard sir, I just heard the most delicious news. Well, why don't you run make a friend and tell them all about it?
I
Believe needs a tax write-off. So he wants the show to flop
That's why he cast nanny fine to guarantee a total disaster. I
Knew it. I
Knew she had no talent people will be walking out in the middle of her performance just like one of your dates
Well, we can't tell her she'll be crushed I know
On the other hand if if I don't tell her then she'll be publicly humiliated opening night. I know it's a win-win situation
Maggie if you want to go to the Hamptons, you're gonna have to ask your father when he's watching Masterpiece Theatre
Yes, just when his chin drops down to his chest, but before he starts snoring
Oh sure, that's how I got my race
We're doing the death scene places everybody Oh Maggie I gotta go I gotta go plunge a knife into my heart
Boy, I'm sounding more like my mother every day
Felipe I gotta ask you a question. I don't know what my motivation is here. Why does Julia kill herself?
Because without her Romeo she has no reason to live
Oh could tell this play was written by a man
What she must be sleeping with him I slept with him I got two lines I got Romeo
Okay Romeo drink your poison
Here's to my love
Thy drugs act quick thus with a kiss I
Die now Juliet awakens
Oh
Romeo I see poison I
See poison has been your timeless end Oh Cheryl
Oh
Happy dagger, this is my sheath
They're rust and let me die
Oh
She's perfect this play will die faster than she does
And now Romeo and Juliet ascend to heaven
oh
Wow!
Oh!
Oh, boy!
Don't worry!
I'm okay!
Oh, but it looks like Romeo's got quite a wedgie going on up there.
Hi!
Hi.
Gee, you know, that harness really chafes.
Boy, that Mary Martin must have had to hide like a rhino.
Cindy, I know you.
Well, I have done six Broadway shows and several national tours.
No, no, it was a commercial.
You're the less than fresh girl!
Oh, Mr. Sheffield!
No, no, people, people, please!
Come on, back off!
Get away!
Let the man breathe.
Give her some air.
Gee, God, she's sleeping with everybody.
Watch, next year she'll have her own sitcom.
Miss Fine, I owe you an apology.
You owe me an apology?
Oh, yeah, right.
I was selfish and thoughtless and I'm extremely sorry.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Sheffield.
I'm sorry I called you a duty head.
Apology accepted.
You know, we shouldn't fight anymore.
It's so hard on Noyles.
Yeah, I know.
Listen, I need to talk to you about this play.
Maybe you'd better sit down.
Oh, okay.
I think I know what you're going to say, though.
No, I doubt that.
Yes, I do.
You're going to say that you and the kids really need me at home
and the mansion is a mess and I don't belong in this play
and, well, you'd be absolutely right.
I would?
Yeah, isn't that what you were going to say?
Oh, yes, yes, that was exactly what...
You read my mind.
I thought Glee of Wayans runs in my family.
I got an ampola that predicted Hurricane Andrew.
For the first time in history,
there wasn't a single Jew on Miami Beach.
Come on, I'm going to take you home.
I just thought that Philip isn't too disappointed.
I mean, he really was counting on me.
Well, Miss Fine, a talent like yours doesn't come along every day.
True, but you know, between you, me and the Pillars,
that Philip is not the greatest director in the world.
And if I'm going to make my big Broadway debut,
I should do it right in one of your plays.
Now back to Masterpiece Theatre, Part 26,
The Lords of Thysbury.
Psst, Maggie, make your move.
Hi, Dad.
Oh.
Are you asleep?
Mmm, yeah.
Are you going to let me go to the Hamptons?
Mmm, sure, honey.
When Miss Fine gets her next raise.
Ever since Alastair Cook left, he doesn't sleep as well.
Yeah.
Lunch!
Oh, good.
Hello?
People?
Oh, people?
Where fought on, everyone?
Hello?
Hi.