WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
You're watching Channel 36's
"Power News Live at Five."
We've got the most
high school sports,
the most lottery numbers,
and the most weather
in the Tri-Swamp area.
It's news time!
Good evening,
I'm Brynn DeRose.
And I'm Slade Austin.
Tonight on "Power News,"
we reveal who Donald Trump
is running against
for President.
Plus, we'll show you
the winning lottery numbers.
Could 67 be one of them?
Two prisoners have escaped
from the Coral Palms
sheriff's station
in a daring daylight jailbreak.
The men, identified
as Gregory Stickney
and Larry Sherbert
were arrested after
a routine traffic stop
revealed a cache
of automatic weapons.
Less than 12 hours later,
the men escaped
by creating a disturbance
in their cell.
Well, they started kissing,
which I'm fine with...
really, I am,
kiss whoever you want...
except they were both men.
Tito Amendola was also
in holding at the time
and witnessed the jailbreak.
I do a lot of meth.
The sheriff's office is
coordinating their search
with local and state police.
If you're watching,
Greg and Larry,
and I know you are,
my men and I will not rest
until we find you.
That's right,
we're coming for you.
Strong words, and moving on,
what if you were going
through a drive-thru,
and a puppy dog
took your order?
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.com/
The cops are looking for us,
and a madman wants us dead.
We should be laying low
until the Nine-Nine gets here.
Yeah, but we don't know
when that's gonna be,
and we need food and supplies.
Okay, I'll get some water.
Holt, are you trying
to draw attention to us?
Nobody drinks water here.
Choose something blue or green.
Okay, I guess
I'll go in for, uh,
the Blazing Blue Rad-berry
Cooler Xtreme: Code Rad.
Good choice.
I should probably get
some body spray as well.
What sounds better,
Liquid Moan or Turnpike?
We only have $17 to our name.
We can't spend five
of it on this.
I know, but I'm about to see
Amy for the first time
in forever, and I want
to smell like a...
"hot New Jersey breeze," ugh.
Good call.
All right, let's get
out of here.
And in Coral Palms,
law enforcement
still is searching
for a pair of fugitives
who broke out of jail
earlier this evening.
Greg Stickney
and Larry Sherbert
are believed to be
unarmed but dangerous.
Liquid Moan, nice.
I wore this to Swampsgiving
last year... cleaned up.
Right on, bro.
Oh, we have a promotion
on the Code Rad.
- It comes with a free cigarette.
- Oh, no.
That doesn't matter.
We don't need it.
Well, if you don't want it,
I'll take it.
No, no, no.
Don't do that... smoking is bad.
You should quit smoking
right now.
Hey...
Ahh.
We seem to be in the clear.
- Are you hurt?
- Yeah.
I got caught on top
of the fence.
Check out my calf...
it's like Scratch City.
How about you?
I'm fine, except I was impaled
on a metal pipe.
Oh, my God!
It's gonna be fine.
I got rifles, vests,
flash grenades...
Chips, dips,
ice cream sammies...
I'm pretty sure there's gonna
be snacks in Florida, Scully.
Pretty sure?
Do you arrest someone if you're
pretty sure they're guilty?
No, Amy,
you wait till you get all the facts!
Hey, okay, everyone,
let's just try to bring things
we actually need
for the mission.
Really?
Then what is this?
Oh, it's a book of 4,000
essential photos of Nikolaj
for me to show Jake.
All right, bad news.
I talked to
Captain Stentley again.
He still won't give us
permission to go to Florida.
I even brought out the big guns.
Left, right, left, right,
both, both, both.
That's so cool!
I still can't let you
go to Florida, though.
Terry feels like a whore.
He said if we disobey him,
there'll be tire consequences.
I think he meant dire.
Guy's real dumb.
Who's with me?
Great, Hitchcock's in.
Who else?
I actually had a question.
How mad would everyone be
if I just bailed?
Shut up, Hitchcock.
Obviously, we're all going.
What's up, squadron?
I'm airplane ready,
and I'm T-minus 30
from my Ambies kicking in,
so let's take it
to the skies.
Yeah, about that.
Um, there were no tickets left.
But I brought my minivan, so...
Road trip!
I went to a 24-hour vet
and got surgical supplies.
I was in and out like a ninja.
Needles, needles, need...
whoa!
So many dogs!
I'll need your assistance.
You'll have to pull out the pipe
and stitch up the wound.
All right.
This is gonna hurt.
But I'm gonna get you
through it.
Oh, God, I'm gonna throw
up into your cut.
Ahhh, I saw inside of you.
How are humans alive?
Okay, uh, I'll do the surgery,
and, uh, you just breathe, okay?
We'll get you through this.
Okay.
Ugh, what was that sound?
I did not like
that squish sound.
The pipe has been removed.
Now...
I'm sewing myself up.
Okay, this is almost over.
You're doing great.
Just keep talking.
Keep talking.
Talking about what?
Uh, tell me about Amy, hmm?
You must be excited to see her.
Very much, you know.
Oh, God, what if it
doesn't go well?
We haven't seen each other
in a while,
and what if it's weird?
- Uhhh!
- Keep going, keep going.
You're doing so well.
Why would it be weird?
I don't know.
I mean, maybe we've grown apart.
Maybe she'll be repulsed
by my frosted tips.
I was gonna defrost them before
I saw her for the first time.
I'm sure it will be magical
when you see her.
And...
guess what?
- What?
- I'm done.
I've sewn myself up.
- Huh.
- You did great, buddy.
I'm proud of you.
I can't believe I did it.
I'm so strong.
Ooh, we're crossing
into Virginia.
Virginia is not
technically a state,
but a commonwealth.
Oof, poor Jake.
Uhh, this might be
the Ambies speaking,
but this in-flight movie sucks.
So, uh, you already
moved the twins
onto a booster seat, huh?
Aren't they a little
young for that?
They're four.
Nikolaj is four,
but we're sticking
with the car seat
as long as possible,
but you know me...
I'm a "safety at all costs"
kind of dad.
Mm-hmm.
Sarge, I need to go
to the bathroom.
We just stopped for gas.
I asked you if you had to go.
I didn't have to then.
So does this van have
side-impact airbags?
Not in the back.
Oh. Interesting.
No judgment here.
Sarge, I have to pee now too.
Seriously?
You, Diaz?
Look, I'll turn off
at the next exit, okay?
I have to pee really badly.
Hot.
- What?
- Hitchcock!
- Guys, enough!
- Sarge...
Yeah, I know!
You got to pee, I got it!
- No, brake lights!
- Oh, crap.
Everyone hang on!
There's no side-impact airbags!
Did you get breakfast?
I tried, but I got recognized.
Do I know you from somewhere?
Do you watch a lot
of pornography?
'Cause I'm in most of it.
Oh, boy.
What if you were followed?
I don't think it's safe
to stay here.
Where are we gonna go?
- The cops?
- Or Figgis!
Do we have any weapons?
I have the pipe
we pulled out of me.
I would sooner surrender
than go anywhere near
your gooey body pipe.
Oh, no, I'm gonna do it.
- Oh!
- Jake?
Amy...
It's so good to see you.
Thank you guys
so much for coming.
I can't wait to catch up
with all of you
when this is done.
My dad died, and...
Again, when this is done,
Hitchcock.
Gina, you look like
a fresh wizard,
and I love it.
So we know that Figgis
is in Coral Palms,
but we don't know where he is,
and we don't know how many
guys he's got with him.
The plan is to lure them into
the Fun Zone and ambush them.
- Any questions?
- Yes, did you miss us?
Did you ever
look up at the moon
and wonder if I was
looking at it too?
- Yes.
- Knew it.
All right, once we get
to the Fun Zone,
I'll fill everyone in
on the mission details.
You guys come with me.
Captain, you stay here and rest.
What?
I don't need to rest.
I'm in peak condition.
All right, then stand up.
Easy.
I love standing up.
Yeah, you're staying here.
Aw, Captain,
don't worry, okay?
My sleeping pills
are doing their job,
and I can stay here
and take care of you, okay?
Terry, I'm gonna
need your gun.
That's not happening.
All right, I'll use my own.
Oops-a-daisy.
That is adorable.
Where did you get that?
Vending machine
at a rest stop.
Give me that.
Just don't let Captain Holt die.
And stay on your phone for
logistical support as planned.
Now come on, guys,
let's get ready.
Hey, we never really
got a chance to say hi.
Yeah. Hi.
Hi.
Oh, my God, everyone,
Jake and Amy are going to kiss
for the first time
in six months.
Let those Nicholas Sparks fly.
So everyone's just
gonna watch us?
Yes!
Now get to it, you lovebirds.
Here we go.
Come on, man.
How did you get there so fast?
- Love finds a way.
- Ugh.
Welcome to the Fun Zone.
I know the manager, and he's
agreed to shut the place down
for the day, so there won't
be any civilians around.
Smart.
You put up all these fake signs
about a major
health code violation.
No, those are actually
always there...
something about lead being in
the air and water and ground.
Anyways, you all have
your assignments.
Let's plan an ambush.
Nine-Nine! NineNine!
Chills, you guys.
Literally, chills.
Hey there, Nikolaj.
It's your papa.
If you're watching this,
something bad has
happened to me.
But I want you to know
that I love you very much.
You want to stop filming
yourself and help me with
these many items I'm carrying?
Sorry, I was making
a video for my son.
You know, in case
I never see him again.
Do you not do that
for your kids?
Of course I do.
I make those kind of videos
all the time.
You know, in fact, I was about
to do one right now.
Hey... hey, girls.
It's me, Daddy.
If you're seeing this,
I'm dead.
But I want you to know
that I love you now and forever.
Okay, time for a lullaby,
sung in your native Latvian.
Ligo! Ligo! Ligo!
Yeah, yeah, lullaby time.
Look.
Go to sleep, Daddy's dead
But his ghost's
always watching
What the hell are
you guys doing?
Good call.
Blocking the door.
Keep it up, smorty-pants.
- Oh...
- Uh...
Mwah.
One of our classic
forehead smooches,
just like I planned.
- This is weird.
- Should we have sex?
- What?
- Huh?
Yeah.
I mean, no.
No, things aren't weird,
or no to the sex?
- Maybe we should just...
- You're right.
Just concentrate on Figgis,
and we'll figure this out later.
No, I was gonna say
maybe we should talk,
but yeah, it can wait
till after Figgis.
Ah.
We have the rest
of our lives to talk.
Yeah, unless he
kills us first.
What a weird joke.
Regret saying that one.
Wow, things are clickin'.
I'm gonna go make sure
there's enough balls in...
in the ball pit.
Yup.
Important to get on them balls.
What is wrong with me?
So then Trevor sends me
a text, and he's like,
"At this point, I hate you."
I'm like, "Oh, really?
'Cause you didn't
hate me last week."
Trevor sounds like a dog.
Right?
God, I missed our daily dishes.
Me too.
I'm sorry I'm not
reciprocating
with "hot goss" of my own.
I'm just worried
about the Nine-Nine.
Sir, they're gonna be fine.
They're my squad.
I should be there with them.
This is killing me.
Well, I'm not gonna let it.
Let's go.
But my wound, Gina.
Sir, with your brain
and my body...
and my brain...
we make one unstoppable unit.
Now climb aboard, sir.
And let's go.
Oof.
All right, everybody ready?
Good.
Let's set this trap.
Hello.
- Hello, Figgis.
- Peralta.
Congratulations
on escaping prison.
Thank you.
Congrats on sucking.
You know, I'm bored.
I'd love to kill you tonight.
So where you hiding?
Wouldn't you like you know?
Round one.
You're never gonna find me.
I'm invisible.
Mommy, I won!
I won a big pwize!
Downtown!
I'm everywhere,
and I'm nowhere.
And I'm coming for you.
Peace out, loser.
He's at the Fun Zone.
Gear up.
This ends tonight.
Uh!
- Ow!
- Oh, sorry, babe.
What were you aiming for?
Hey, got you a bag
of Blue Rad-berry slushie
for the swelling.
I would've just gotten ice,
but a possum died
in the ice machine.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Why do we keep
hurting each other?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
It just feels like we're not...
- On the same page.
- Clicking.
That was basically
the same thing.
- I count that.
- Yeah.
Look, I know this
isn't the right time
for some big talk,
but I just...
want us to be normal again.
Yeah, me too.
I hope you're a better
kisser than Holt.
- What?
- Why did I say that?
Why did you kiss Holt?
I didn't. I did.
We did it to get out of jail,
but it didn't mean anything.
Just forget I said
anything, right?
Rewind.
- And kiss.
- Jake...
You want to know
if there was tongue.
I can tell you,
decidedly there was not.
No, Jake.
Figgis is here.
Okay, well, good talk.
Don't die.
Holt had very soft lips.
Wish I hadn't said
that one either.
- We should get into positions.
- Yeah, okay.
Hey, kill the lights!
Figgis is here!
Excuse me, ma'am,
this dolly's being used.
Broccoli Che visto?
It's being used.
Quanti erala Vito la Bella?
Tutto matro lamente?
Just bring it back
when you're done.
Ah! Garbanzo marinara!
Pizzería restaurante!
Ahh!
Jackpot.
Let's do this.
And how am I supposed
to get all the way up there?
Gracefully.
- Boost my bottom!
- I'm boosting!
Boost my bottom!
I'm boosting!
Boost it!
Ah. All right...
stick shift.
I can't drive stick shift.
You're gonna have to drive.
How? My leg doesn't work.
Sir, I am a dancer.
I will be your legs.
Clutch in.
- Okay.
- Clutch out.
- Oh!
- Hoo-hoo!
We are the best driver
in the world!
Spread out and find 'em.
Bogie headed to the ball pit.
Is that all you got?
I'll take your best shot
I'll take your best shot,
I'll take your best shot!
Boom  - Here comes the.
Boom  - Ready or not.
Here comes the boys
from the South
- Is that all you got?
- I'll take your best shot.
- Well, it's all right
- I'll take your best shot
- Boom.
Here comes the  - Boom.
Ready or not,
ha ha, how you like me now?
Peralta...
Holt.
I know you're here.
I'm gonna kill you.
- I don't think so.
- Oh...
Put down the weapon, Figgis.
There you go.
Oh, yes.
I've been waiting for this
moment a long time.
You ruined my life.
I had to live in Florida
for six months!
It's the worst.
Have you tried
the pizza down here?
Yeah, it's the most disgusting
thing I've ever tasted.
It somehow burned my mouth
and is cold at the same time.
But none of that changes
the fact that you're about
to go to prison for
the rest of your life.
Drop it, Sherbert!
What? No!
I've been everywhere,
and I finally spotted your minivan
with the New York plates
parked around back.
We already got all your friends.
So drop it.
You don't understand.
I'm a detective with the NYPD.
This is Jimmy Figgis;
he's wanted by the FBI.
No, I'm Constantine Binvoglio,
and I came here to repair
a skee ball machine
on the the fritz, but suddenly
he's trying to kill me.
He's lying.
"Constantine Binvoglio."
It's clearly a name
he just made up.
I'm very impressed.
That was pretty good.
I will shoot you, Sherbert.
All right, fine,
I will put down my weapon,
but you have to promise me
you will not let this man go.
Okay, well, we're gonna
cuff everyone,
and then we're gonna
sort this all out.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thanks, Sheriff.
No!
Now let's me and you
take a little walk.
Ooh.
How do you think you're
getting out of this, Figgis?
Do you even have a plan?
I'm gonna hold you hostage
to get away.
Then I'm gonna drive
to a gas station
where I'll steal a clean car
and head for the airport,
where I'll buy a ticket
with my false ID,
then kill you in the parking lot
and disappear again.
Pfft.
You're scrambling.
Look, I told you, we're NYPD.
- Yeah, right.
- I can prove it.
Look up "Brooklyn detective
attacked by birds."
You'll see an article
with a photo of me.
Officer down.
All available units respond.
I'm gonna give you a window,
and you're gonna go after Jake.
My name is Detective
Rosa Diaz, NYPD.
- Get back.
- I'm reaching for my badge.
Keep walking.
Let him go.
Put that gun down, or he dies.
He's not gonna shoot me.
He needs me alive
to get out of here.
Yeah, you willing
to take that bet?
I wouldn't.
Now put the gun down.
Oh!
You shot him!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I shot you.
I thought that's
what the nod meant.
It was. It was awesome.
It was actually just like
the end of "Speed,"
which is a pretty good movie.
It's not as good as "Die Hard."
"Die Hard"'s perfect.
Okay, Jake, I'm gonna
go after Figgis.
Yeah, I was gonna say, you
should keep going after Figgis.
Same page, still.
Get out of the car!
Young Jeezy take the wheel!
Freeze, punk!
Yeah, freeze, punk!
Gina, where did you
get that gun?
Lost and found at
the storage facility.
They have boxes of 'em.
They're everywhere.
Hey, Figgis.
My fiancé, Adrian Pimento,
said when I caught you,
I should read you this letter.
"I want to lick the skin
off your body, baby."
Oh, that side's for me.
"I want to rip the skin
off your body, Jimmy."
We're sorry we
doubted you, sir.
You really saved our butts.
I can't take credit for that.
Gina Linetti is the real
hero here.
But isn't Gina Linetti
more of a state of mind?
Like, in a way, we were all
Gina Linetti today.
Gina, let's take this Gina
to the hospital.
Hey, how's the sheriff?
Well, he keeps yelling,
"Disability for life!"
So I think he's fine.
Also, Coral Palms PD
found your marshal
at Figgis's hideout,
alive at well.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah. How are you doing?
Fine... you know, just getting
bandaged up.
Actually, can you
give us a second?
Thanks.
It hurts so bad.
I just didn't want
to seem weak
in front of EMT Craig.
So I know this
is weird to say,
because I just shot you,
but it feels like we're
back in sync now.
Yeah, I mean, as in sync
as I've ever been
with someone who just shot me.
I love you.
I love you too.
Hey, do you happen
to know my blood type?
Yeah. B positive.
Well, guessed wrong.
Hey, Craig?
Hey, Captain Stentley,
we're back.
How was Florida?
- It was fine.
- A lot of college girls.
Come on, man.
Now, before you say anything,
I know we disobeyed
a direct order.
Sergeant, relax, okay?
Your friends were in trouble;
you did what you had to do.
And now I got to do
what I got to do.
Oh, no, a memorandum
of admonishment?
Much worse... you're never
gonna see the sun again.
Your families... they're gonna
forget your faces.
You'll eat lunch at dinnertime
and dinner at breakfast.
And you'll...
Ah, what was I talking about?
I totally lost my train.
- You were punishing us.
- Yes, thank you.
Ah!
I'm transferring the whole squad
to the night shift.
Noooo!
Yes.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.com/