Oh
Was it as good for you as it was for me actually Niles I was faking it
Hi sweetie see some of the kids are going to the Hamptons for the weekend. Oh great. Will there be boys there?
Maybe a few fun parents. Who cares? They'll just get in the way anyway
Go have a blast. We don't have enough to tell your father
Really? Oh sure and when I'm fired and you're in the convent, we'll write each other letters and laugh about this
But Maxwell, how can you say no to working with Philippe? He's an avant-garde genius
Guilty as charged and I've put a new twist on the tragedy
We follow Romeo and Juliet to heaven and have a happy ending
You're really writing one of the greatest love stories of all time. We're adding a few scenes, but we're taking out others
Which ones the ones that don't work?
Well, I'm sorry fully but we British have a thing about mutilating Shakespeare the Queen comes and hits you with her purse
But I bet you have a big name to star. I'm looking for an unknown a fresh face with a unique voice
I found my Juliet
She was working in a bridal shop and flashing Queen's till her boyfriend kicked her out in one of those crushing scenes
What was she to do? Where was she to go? She was out on her fanny
So over the bridge and flashing to the Sheffield's door. She was there to sell makeup but the father saw more
She had style, she had flair, she was there. That's how she became the nanny
Who would have guessed that the girl we described
Was just exactly what the doctor prescribed
Now the father finds her reguiling, watch out Cece
And the kids are actually smiling, such what a thing
She's the lady in red when everybody else is wearing tan
The flashy girl from Flushing, the nanny named Fran
Can you imagine anything more ridiculous than me doing Shakespeare?
Well yes, people paying to see it
I'll have you know that in high school I played the Reverend Mother in the Sound of Music
I put a low scoop neck into my nun's habit and those hills were alive
We did the Sound of Music, I played the Baroness
It was an all-boys school
Thank God I didn't play the guitar, I would have been Maria
Fran, you can't be in the play
Yeah, who would do our laundry, clean our room? We don't have standing foot
Well, the same person that always does, Niles
Besides if I do it, it would only be for a couple of weeks
Actually, I could rehearse while the kids are at school
I think not
Why think you not? I could use a life outside of this house
Me too, which is why you should let me go to the Hamptons
Nice try, forget it
Look Miss Fine, taking care of the children is a full-time job
Oh and I suppose it was my idea to have three?
What you do in your spare time is entirely your own affair
I'm simply trying to protect you from having an embarrassing theatrical experience
We know what that's like, don't we sir?
You know, if some people aren't a little more supportive
I might omit them from my Oscar speech
Tony, Miss Fine, you'd win a Tony, not an Oscar
Actually, for an off-Broadway performance, Miss Fine would win the OB
She's not going to win anything
Well, thank you for that vote of confidence, that's it
I'm playing Juliet and nothing is going to stop me
And I'm going to the Hamptons
Sit down Margaret
I'm going to the Hamptons
Okay
Okay Niles, will you play Romeo?
Isn't he too old?
Well actually, Juliet's supposed to be my age so it's not like Franz
Not perfect for the role
I warn you, my acting prowess may blow you off the stage
They're still talking about my baroness
I can't stop thinking about it and I didn't even see it
And I spent my summers in Stratford upon Avon
I spent my summers selling Avon
Oh, she doth teach the torches to burn bright
It seems she hangs upon the cheek of night
Niles, don't I come in here somewhere?
Anon, anon, beauty too rich for use for a...
Alright, back off baroness
And by the way, you're supposed to dust the scenery, not chew it
Well, could they show me how it's done, Mistress Fine?
Well, I will if you'll just shut it up if...
Oh, for a falconer's voice to lure this tassel gentile back again
It's gentle, not gentile
How should I know? Did I look down his tights?
I still can't understand why Philippe would hire Miss Fine to play Juliet
Please, only an idiot would hire her to do anything
In the theater
Oh, oh, Mr. Sheffield, if you've got a minute I could use your help
That's the understatement of the century
Meanwhile, if we put an apple in his mouth we can have a luau
Let me see
Oh, I just love this play
More torches here, ah, sirrah, by my fey it waxes late
See, that's exactly what I'm talking about
With Alice Faye and why she waxing during a party
Good luck
Shall I play Romeo to your Juliet?
Four, three, two, what took you so long?
All right, so now we're star-crossed lovers
Let's get some physical realism into this, shall we?
Oh, Mr. Sheffield
No, I mean I'm going to put you on your balcony
Oh, okay
All right, now Juliet is dreaming of her Romeo
And she says...
I'm a
Oh, speak again, bright angel
Oh, Romeo, Romeo
Yes, no, maybe we could have a little more lilting
Just a bit more melodic
Oh, sure, sure, sure, melodic
Oh, Romeo, Romeo
Yeah, just a little too melodic, I think
Let me show you
Okay, sure, he's going to show us
Oh, Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name
Wow, you British guys really know how to play women
We did this play in college
Oh, you must have been the perfect Romeo
No, I was Friar Lawrence, actually
That's the problem going to school with Jeremy Irons
All right, let's go on
Okay
Romeo, def thy name and take all of me
I take thee at thy word
Call me but love and I'll be new baptized
You know, if I were directing this I'd go in a whole different direction
Good night, good night
Parting is such sweet sorrow
Sleep dwell in thine eyes, peace in thy breast
How would I were sleep and peace so sweet to rest?
You know, because this Slubby-Dubby stuff has just been done to death
You know?
Much better
Yeah, I think I'm starting to get the hang of it now
Of course I'm going to need a lot of coaching
I'm going to suck out all your blood and bury you alive
You don't scare me
All right, fine, I'm the Cici Monster
And I'm going to marry dad and send you away to boarding school
We're just going to play a game
But I'm going to get you at the end of the game
And then we're going to have a game
That's right
You scare me!
All right, fine. I'm the Cece Monster.
And I'm gonna marry Dad and send you away to boarding school!
Ah!
Children! Children! Children!
Be quiet!
Geez, Dad, you don't have to scream about it.
Look, I already sent you to bed five times.
What are you doing still up?
Well, I'm not tired.
Well, maybe that has something to do with the pound of chocolate
I told you not to eat.
You know, I think it was a gallon of cola you told me not to drink.
And what's your excuse?
Well, he took me in wrong.
Obviously. You got out.
Now, come on. Off the bed, both of you.
Just give me one good reason why I can't go to the Hamptons.
I won't let you.
Look, Margaret, you're much too young to go away for the weekend.
By the time Juliet was my age,
she had already gotten married, had sex, and died.
Well, now you see what happens when you don't listen to your father.
Niles, I'm thinking of changing the children's bedtime.
Oh, to when, sir?
Right after school.
I can't believe Miss Fine isn't back yet.
I can't believe what's happened to my roast.
It's starting to bear a strange resemblance to Hume Cronin.
I mean, how much rehearsal can one person need?
Oh, right.
But still...
Oh, hi, guys. For sooth, am I.
Poop.
Dinner is coming right up.
Oh, Niles, I already ate.
You couldn't have called?
Well... Never mind.
Ruined, anyway.
Boy, is he moody.
Well, you are rather late.
What are you two on, the same cycle?
What's the problem?
Oh, you couldn't handle the kids?
Oh, don't make me laugh.
What, do you think the minute you leave, the entire house falls apart?
Oh, well...
No, don't go in there.
Why not?
We can use the back stairs. They're closer.
No, they're not.
Yes, they are.
Oh, not?
Oh, so I measured.
OK.
Too slow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, this place looks worse than when my mother ransacked my bedroom
and I'm looking for my diary.
Well, I was looking for my glasses.
What do you have, a reading emergency?
So, what were you doing all evening?
I was at rehearsal.
Well, I called. Rehearsal was over at eight.
Well, we went out after.
Who's we?
Oh, you know, Romeo, Mercutio, Tybalt, the gang.
Oh, I'm sorry. It was an accident.
So was that.
Boy, you leave the house for a couple hours,
you come back and it's a pigsty.
Yeah, well, maybe if you'd been here,
your children wouldn't have been running amuck.
Oh, so when they're sweet, adorable angels,
they're your children, and when they're amuck, they're mine.
Well, you are the nanny.
And that's all you want me to be.
Now I'm getting one of my headaches.
You know what I think?
You are jealous because Philippe discovered something
that was right under your nose.
And what would that be exactly?
My star quality.
That's rather like discovering the atomic bomb.
Sounds good in theory, but millions will suffer.
Well, that's it. I'm going home to my mother.
No, don't bother. I'm sleeping on the couch.
If we're splitting up, I get Niles.
At least you couldn't afford him.
Not on what you pay me.
It's always the butler who suffers.
Oh.
I'm working.
Pretend I'm not here. That's how I get through the day.
Oh, hello, Niles.
Would you mind telling Mr. Sheffield that I'm going to rehearsal?
Unless, of course, he'd like me to sit by his feet and peel him a grape.
Well, that's my job, but you can wave the fan.
Well, you can tell the nanny
that I wouldn't dream of standing in the way of her aspirations,
no matter how ludicrous they might be.
Well, tell Mr. Sheffield that I am a ground woman
and can find fulfillment any way I choose
and that he is a duty head.
To synopsize her, you are a duty head.
So that's the one you choose to repeat.
Translate as prerogative.
I don't think I've ever met a more infuriating, irritating woman.
Hello, hello.
Think hard, sir.
I just heard the most delicious news.
Well, why don't you run, make a friend and tell them all about it?
Philippe needs a tax write-off, so he wants the show to flop.
That's why he cast Nanny Fine, to guarantee a total disaster.
I knew it!
I knew she had no talent.
People will be walking out in the middle of her performance.
Just like one of your dates.
Well, we can't tell her. She'll be crushed.
I know.
On the other hand, if I don't tell her,
then she'll be publicly humiliated opening night.
I know. It's a win-win situation.
Maggie, if you want to go to the Hamptons,
you're going to have to ask your father
when he's watching Masterpiece Theatre.
Yes, just when his chin drops down to his chest,
but before he starts snoring.
Well, sure, that's how I got my raise.
We're doing the death scene. Places, everybody.
Oh, Maggie, I gotta go.
I gotta go plunge a knife into my heart.
Boy, I'm sounding more like my mother when I'm in the bathroom.
Boy, I'm sounding more like my mother every time.
Oh, uh, Philippe, I gotta ask you a question.
I don't know what my motivation is here.
Why does Juliet kill herself?
Because without her Romeo, she has no reason to live.
Oh. You could tell this play was written by a man.
I don't know how she got this part.
Well, she must be sleeping with him.
I slept with him. I got two lines.
I got Romeo.
Okay.
Romeo, drink your poison.
Here's to my love.
Thy drugs act quick, thus with a kiss.
I die.
Now, Juliet awakens.
Aye, what a night.
Oh, Romeo, I see poison.
I see poison hath been your timeless end.
Oh, Cheryl.
Oh, happy dagger, this is thy sheath.
There rust and let me die.
Ah!
Oh!
Hey! Hey!
Ah!
She's perfect.
This play will die faster than she does.
Aye.
And now Romeo and Juliet ascend to heaven.
My Lord Romeo.
I follow thee to heaven.
Whoa!
Hi! Hey!
You guys!
Heaven on God away!
Whoa!
Hey!
Oh!
Whoa!
Hey!
Oh!
Whoa!
Oh, boy!
Don't worry!
I'm okay!
Oh, but it looks like Romeo's got quite a wedgie going on.
Bye!
Hi.
Gee, you know, that harness really chafes.
Boy, that Mary Maughan must have had to hide like a rhino.
Hey, I know you.
Well, I have done six Broadway shows and several national tours.
No, no, it was a commercial.
You're the less than fresh girl!
Oh, Mr. Sheffield!
Who are you, sir?
I'm the new lady.
No, you're not!
You're not!
People! People, please!
Come on, back off!
I'm not!
Get away! Let the man breathe!
Give her some air!
Sheesh!
God, she's sleeping with everybody!
Watch, next year she'll have her own sitcom.
Miss Fine, I owe you an apology.
You owe me an apology?
Oh, yeah, right.
I was selfish and thoughtless, and I'm extremely sorry.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Sheffield.
I'm sorry I called you a duty head.
Apology accepted.
You know, we shouldn't fight anymore. It's so hard on Noyles.
Yeah, I know.
Listen, I need to talk to you about this play.
Maybe you'd better sit down.
Oh, okay.
I think I know what you're gonna say, though.
No, I doubt that.
Yes, I do.
You're gonna say that you and the kids really need me at home,
and the mansion is a mess,
and I don't belong in this play,
and, well, you'd be absolutely right.
I would?
Yeah, isn't that what you were gonna say?
Oh, yes, yes, that was exactly what...
You read my mind.
Our clairvoyance runs in my family.
I got an ampoule of the predicted Hurricane Andrew.
For the first time in history,
there wasn't a single Jew on Miami Beach.
Come on. I'm gonna take you home.
I just thought that Philip isn't too disappointed.
I mean, he really was counting on me.
Well, Miss Fine, a talent like yours
doesn't come along every day.
True.
But you know, between you, me, and the Pillars,
that Philippe is not the greatest director in the world.
And if I'm gonna make my big Broadway debut,
I should do it right.
In one of your plays.
Oh.
Now back to Masterpiece Theater, part 26,
The Lords of Thisbury.
Psst, Maggie, make your move.
Hi, Dad.
Oh.
Are you asleep?
Mm, no.
Are you gonna let me go to the Hamptons?
Mm, sure, honey.
When Miss Fine gets her next raise.
Ever since Alastair Cook left, he doesn't sleep as well.
Oh!
Lunch!
Oh, good.
Hello?
People?
Oh, people.
We're fought on, everyone.
Hello?
Hi.