So, do you recognize any of these men?
I was hiding in the bathroom stall,
so I didn't see his face, but I heard him.
He was singing along to the music at the bar.
Do you remember what he was singing?
I think it was that song, I Want It That Way.
Backstreet Boys. I'm familiar. Okay.
Number one, could you please sing the opening
to I Want It That Way?
Really?
Okay.
You are
my fire
Number two, keep it going.
I want the one desire
Number three, believe when I say
Number four, I want it that way
Tell me why
Ain't nothing but a heartache
Ain't nothing but a mistake
Now number five, I never want to hear you say
Woo!
I want it that way
Ah, chills. Literal chills.
It was number five. Number five killed my brother.
Oh, my God. I forgot about that part.