I didn't know what to say to Turk next and then it happened.
Sir, the door was open. I know. I just love doing that.
What now, Grandpa?
You are going to shut your damn yapper and listen to a change because I got you pegged, sweetheart.
You want to take the easy way out with this surgery because you're scared.
And you're scared because if you try and fail there's only you to blame.
Well, Missy, let me break the door.
down for you, Bobbo style. Life is scary. Get used to it.
And then it seemed like Dr. Kelso wasn't only talking to her.
There are no magical fixes. It's all up to you. So get up off your keister, get out of
here and go start doing the work. What if it's too hard?
Yeah, what if it's too hard? Dirkledon, I have no idea why you're chiming
in, but I'll say this to both of you. Nothing in this world that's worth having.
Hamming comes easy.
I gotta go.
Okay, here it goes.
Oh, this is so weird.
I don't really know what to say.
Sorry I haven't visited much, I've been kinda busy.
That's not true. Why am I lying to a slut with granite?
I just know I really could have used that.
I used you around this week.
I miss you.
Can you tell her I miss her too?
You know what? Never mind.
Because she wouldn't believe it.